http://www.clements.com/terms-conditions

Payment
You may pay for your policy by MasterCard, VISA, American Express, Discover Card, Check or Money Order. Checks and Money Orders should be made payable to Clements Worldwide.
Privacy Policy
Clements Worldwide believes that our clients' personal information should be carefully protected. For this reason, we are committed to protecting your non-public personal information and using it only as appropriate or necessary to service and administer your policy. Our Privacy Policy provides detailed information on our practices and policies as they relate to information collection, information security and information sharing to third parties and to members within our corporate family.
You may view our complete Privacy Policy by clicking here.
Policy Delivery
We will process your information as soon as possible. If any additional information is needed, an Account Executive will contact you within 2 business days. Once your application is approved, we will mail your policy contract along with your declarations page to the address indicated on your application. You may choose to receive your policy by mail or e-mail.
Cancellation Policy
You may cancel your policy at any time. All policy cancellation requests must be submitted to Clements Worldwide in writing by e-mail, fax, or traditional mail. Once coverage is canceled, refunds are available according to the terms and conditions stated in your policy.
Customer Service
Please contact us if you have any questions or require additional information.
Auto Insurance in the U.K.
Auto Insurance in the U.K.
Defense Base Act Insurance (DBA)
Careers in the U.S.
Contact Us
Get a Quote Now
